{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349216437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349216437"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd6aef77-4826-443a-80bf-72ffac918d03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-E-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349221451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349221450"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd6aef77-4826-443a-80bf-72ffac918d03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-E-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349226415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349226415"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd6aef77-4826-443a-80bf-72ffac918d03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-E-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349233487","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349233487"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd6aef77-4826-443a-80bf-72ffac918d03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-I-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349238795","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349238794"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd6aef77-4826-443a-80bf-72ffac918d03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-I-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349245369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349245368"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd6aef77-4826-443a-80bf-72ffac918d03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-I-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349249813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349249813"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd6aef77-4826-443a-80bf-72ffac918d03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-U-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349254694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349254694"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd6aef77-4826-443a-80bf-72ffac918d03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_O-E-U"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349259429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349259429"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd6aef77-4826-443a-80bf-72ffac918d03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349265162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349265162"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd6aef77-4826-443a-80bf-72ffac918d03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349278838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349278838"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349279275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349279275"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349279761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349279761"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349280407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349280407"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349283489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349283489"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349283584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349283584"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349284443","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349284443"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349284861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349284861"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349285690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349285690"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349288692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349288691"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" KWEYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349289742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349289742"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" AMEVALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349290444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349290444"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349290639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349290638"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349291219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349291218"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349292019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349292019"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349294999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349294999"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349295108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349295107"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349295871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349295871"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349296386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349296386"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349296581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349296581"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349297260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349297260"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349300098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349300097"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349300323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349300323"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349301032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349301031"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349304042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349304041"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349304155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349304155"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349304840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349304840"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349305325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349305325"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349306143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349306143"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349309156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349309156"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349309789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349309789"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" PINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349310528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349310528"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349311247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349311247"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349311384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349311383"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349312233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349312232"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349315228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349315227"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349315372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349315372"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349316089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349316089"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349316606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349316605"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349317329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349317329"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349320416","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349320416"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349320853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349320853"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349321350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349321350"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349321475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349321475"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349322231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349322231"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349325272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349325271"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349325384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349325384"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349326144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349326144"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349326519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349326519"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349327607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349327607"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349330438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349330438"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" MBINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349330912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349330912"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349331921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349331921"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349334780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349334780"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349334915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349334915"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349335495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349335494"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349335760","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349335760"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349336376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349336376"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349339695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349339695"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349340411","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349340411"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349340946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349340946"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349341099","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349341099"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349341632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349341632"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349341765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349341765"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349342364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349342364"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349345429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349345429"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349345524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349345524"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349346244","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349346244"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349346667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349346667"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349347627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349347626"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" ZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349350642","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349350641"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349350978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349350978"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349351706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349351706"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349351774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349351774"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349352843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349352843"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349355046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349355046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349355512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349355512"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349357085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349357085"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIIPENDAYO"," userResponse":" NIIPENDAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349358223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349358222"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349361230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349361230"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349362982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349362982"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAZIJUA"," userResponse":" UNAZIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349363459","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349363459"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349364051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349364050"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349364347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349364347"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349365359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349365359"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349368069","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349368068"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349368150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349368150"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 461e102c-3198-41d3-a42b-61484e6b2d92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349379203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349379203"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349385615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349385614"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349387163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349387163"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349391251","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349391250"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349392802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349392801"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349396776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349396776"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349398348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349398348"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349402871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349402870"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349404430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349404429"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349409739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349409739"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349411299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349411298"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349415847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349415847"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349416714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349416713"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" START_ANAKULA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349417399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349417399"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349427958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349427957"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349428072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349428072"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9975e969-72b1-49d3-a2ed-d92228a79725"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349438692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349438692"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82a3e1d8-00d6-4b56-9e80-3d74d34a6170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-2-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349444847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349444847"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82a3e1d8-00d6-4b56-9e80-3d74d34a6170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-9-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349451356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349451356"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82a3e1d8-00d6-4b56-9e80-3d74d34a6170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-8-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349458538","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349458538"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82a3e1d8-00d6-4b56-9e80-3d74d34a6170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-8-0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349470338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349470338"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82a3e1d8-00d6-4b56-9e80-3d74d34a6170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-0-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349476254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349476254"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82a3e1d8-00d6-4b56-9e80-3d74d34a6170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-1-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349482112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349482112"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82a3e1d8-00d6-4b56-9e80-3d74d34a6170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_2-6-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349489493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349489493"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82a3e1d8-00d6-4b56-9e80-3d74d34a6170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-1-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349499154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349499154"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82a3e1d8-00d6-4b56-9e80-3d74d34a6170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-5-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349505824","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349505824"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82a3e1d8-00d6-4b56-9e80-3d74d34a6170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_5-9-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349512347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349512346"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82a3e1d8-00d6-4b56-9e80-3d74d34a6170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_5-9-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349522552","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349522552"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349522935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349522935"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349523171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349523171"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349523484","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349523484"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349523716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349523716"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349527145","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349527144"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349527437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349527437"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349528340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349528339"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349528763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349528763"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349531671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349531671"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349531953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349531953"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349532796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349532796"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349533460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349533460"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349534195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349534195"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349534518","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349534518"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349534791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349534791"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349535106","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349535106"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349535369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349535369"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349539087","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349539087"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349539470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349539470"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349539706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349539706"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349540020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349540020"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349540254","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349540254"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349543683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349543683"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349543976","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349543975"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349544881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349544880"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349545304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349545304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349548196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349548196"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349548478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349548478"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349549320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349549320"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349549984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349549983"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349550716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349550716"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349551043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349551043"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349551316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349551316"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349551629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349551629"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349551892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349551892"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349555375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349555375"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349555437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349555437"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 97aba900-8943-44a1-b368-aed490bbca38"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349566064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349566064"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349566581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349566581"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349567115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349567115"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" MBINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349567348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349567347"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349567551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349567551"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349568203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349568203"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349568277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349568277"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349569690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349569689"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mbingu ni za rangi ya samawati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349572559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349572559"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ni samawati kila wakati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349573142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349573141"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ni samawati kila wakati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349574125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349574125"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ni samawati kila wakati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349574527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349574527"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ni samawati kila wakati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349575441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349575441"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ni samawati kila wakati?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349577971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349577971"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349578414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349578414"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349579086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349579086"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349579369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349579369"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349579483","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349579483"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349580086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349580086"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349581139","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349581139"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini majani ni ya kijani kibichi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349584097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349584097"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIO"," userResponse":" SIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349584311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349584310"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349584943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349584943"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349585600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349585600"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349586014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349586014"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349586869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349586869"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sio ya kijani kibichi kila wakati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349589597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349589597"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349590050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349590050"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349590584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349590584"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349590829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349590829"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349591065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349591064"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349592008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349592007"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini ndizi ni za njano?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJANO"," userResponse":" NJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349594994","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349594993"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbivu ni za njano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349595688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349595687"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbivu ni za njano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIVU"," userResponse":" MBIVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349595989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349595988"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbivu ni za njano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349596299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349596299"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbivu ni za njano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349596983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349596982"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbivu ni za njano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJANO"," userResponse":" NJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349599299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349599298"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349599914","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349599913"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBICHI"," userResponse":" MBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349600176","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349600175"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349600468","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349600468"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349601238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349601237"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349602311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349602310"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi mbichi ni za kijani kibichi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349604995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349604994"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini miavuli ni mieusi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349605475","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349605474"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini miavuli ni mieusi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349606394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349606394"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini miavuli ni mieusi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAVULI"," userResponse":" MIAVULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349606619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349606618"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini miavuli ni mieusi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349607665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349607664"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini miavuli ni mieusi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEUSI"," userResponse":" MIEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349610862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349610862"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miavuli yote si mieusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAVULI"," userResponse":" MIAVULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349611519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349611518"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miavuli yote si mieusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349611882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349611882"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miavuli yote si mieusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349612755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349612754"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miavuli yote si mieusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIEUSI"," userResponse":" MIEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349615467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349615466"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini damu ni nyekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349615939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349615939"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini damu ni nyekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349616491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349616491"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini damu ni nyekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAMU"," userResponse":" DAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349616618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349616618"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini damu ni nyekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349617782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349617782"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini damu ni nyekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349620599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349620598"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna madini kwenye damu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349621373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349621373"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna madini kwenye damu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADINI"," userResponse":" MADINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349621896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349621895"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna madini kwenye damu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349622578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349622577"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna madini kwenye damu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAMU"," userResponse":" DAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349625670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349625669"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yanaifanya damu kuwa nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAIFANYA"," userResponse":" YANAIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349626292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349626291"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yanaifanya damu kuwa nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAMU"," userResponse":" DAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349626770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349626769"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yanaifanya damu kuwa nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349627692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349627691"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yanaifanya damu kuwa nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349630236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349630235"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349630739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349630738"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349631362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349631362"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMVI"," userResponse":" CHUMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349631613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349631612"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349632604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349632604"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349635397","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349635396"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349635479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349635479"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 7d0b289a-97ef-45f5-845e-63634d957e3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349644901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349644901"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd0396b3-d7c9-49e3-a5cb-57e23251863b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_O-E-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349648327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349648327"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd0396b3-d7c9-49e3-a5cb-57e23251863b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-I-U"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349652258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349652258"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd0396b3-d7c9-49e3-a5cb-57e23251863b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-A-O"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349656756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349656756"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd0396b3-d7c9-49e3-a5cb-57e23251863b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-O-U"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349660722","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349660722"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd0396b3-d7c9-49e3-a5cb-57e23251863b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_O-E-A"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349664140","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349664140"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd0396b3-d7c9-49e3-a5cb-57e23251863b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-E-O"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349668115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349668115"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd0396b3-d7c9-49e3-a5cb-57e23251863b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_I-A-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349671790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349671790"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd0396b3-d7c9-49e3-a5cb-57e23251863b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_O-A-U"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349675286","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349675286"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd0396b3-d7c9-49e3-a5cb-57e23251863b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_I-A-U"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349679149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349679149"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd0396b3-d7c9-49e3-a5cb-57e23251863b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_O-U-A"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349684894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349684893"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" bd0396b3-d7c9-49e3-a5cb-57e23251863b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_A_O-U-A"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349697896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349697895"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" afa97bac-8612-4868-8e23-4b09dfa4c161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-3-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349705024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349705024"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" afa97bac-8612-4868-8e23-4b09dfa4c161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-9-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349711148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349711148"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" afa97bac-8612-4868-8e23-4b09dfa4c161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_7-5-8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349717856","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349717856"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" afa97bac-8612-4868-8e23-4b09dfa4c161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_2-7-9"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349728978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349728978"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" afa97bac-8612-4868-8e23-4b09dfa4c161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_1-6-0"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349735598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349735598"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" afa97bac-8612-4868-8e23-4b09dfa4c161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-8-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349742640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349742640"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" afa97bac-8612-4868-8e23-4b09dfa4c161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-1-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349748792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349748792"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" afa97bac-8612-4868-8e23-4b09dfa4c161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349754110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349754110"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" afa97bac-8612-4868-8e23-4b09dfa4c161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_0-3-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349760218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349760218"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" afa97bac-8612-4868-8e23-4b09dfa4c161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_7-1-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349765884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349765884"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" afa97bac-8612-4868-8e23-4b09dfa4c161"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_7-1-8"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349779811","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349779810"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1363133d-513b-47e4-96df-f3d1fb463aba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_6-3-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349785745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349785745"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1363133d-513b-47e4-96df-f3d1fb463aba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_9-4-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349792679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349792679"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1363133d-513b-47e4-96df-f3d1fb463aba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_4-6-8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349800813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349800813"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1363133d-513b-47e4-96df-f3d1fb463aba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-5-9"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349807356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349807356"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1363133d-513b-47e4-96df-f3d1fb463aba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_5-6-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349812553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349812553"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1363133d-513b-47e4-96df-f3d1fb463aba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-1-8"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349819060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349819060"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1363133d-513b-47e4-96df-f3d1fb463aba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349824506","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349824506"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1363133d-513b-47e4-96df-f3d1fb463aba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349831553","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349831552"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1363133d-513b-47e4-96df-f3d1fb463aba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-9-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349838515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349838515"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1363133d-513b-47e4-96df-f3d1fb463aba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_0-7-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349845058","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349845058"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1363133d-513b-47e4-96df-f3d1fb463aba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_5_0-7-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349872493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349872492"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2e011c85-505f-4cb2-9699-2c314eb68503"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_E_A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349879119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349879118"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2e011c85-505f-4cb2-9699-2c314eb68503"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_A_E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349885780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349885780"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2e011c85-505f-4cb2-9699-2c314eb68503"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_E_A"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349892395","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349892395"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2e011c85-505f-4cb2-9699-2c314eb68503"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_O_A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349899067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349899067"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2e011c85-505f-4cb2-9699-2c314eb68503"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_O_U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349905705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349905705"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2e011c85-505f-4cb2-9699-2c314eb68503"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_I_U"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349912342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349912342"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2e011c85-505f-4cb2-9699-2c314eb68503"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_O_E"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349918965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349918965"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2e011c85-505f-4cb2-9699-2c314eb68503"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_U_A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349925649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349925649"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2e011c85-505f-4cb2-9699-2c314eb68503"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_O_A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349932292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349932291"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2e011c85-505f-4cb2-9699-2c314eb68503"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_O_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349941933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349941933"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2e011c85-505f-4cb2-9699-2c314eb68503"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.10.rand.say.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_A_O_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349952670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349952670"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349952980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349952980"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349953595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349953595"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349956639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349956638"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349959570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349959569"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349960221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349960221"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349960977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349960976"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349964048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349964047"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" AKIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349965623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349965623"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" ANAZIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349966219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349966218"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349966893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349966893"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349967749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349967749"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349968663","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349968662"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349968779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349968779"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349969299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349969299"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349972077","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349972076"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349973013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349973013"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349973422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349973422"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349973531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349973531"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349974677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349974676"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349974919","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349974919"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349975435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349975434"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349975688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349975688"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349976569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349976568"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349977064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349977064"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349979890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349979889"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349980793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349980792"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349981287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349981287"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349981394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349981394"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349982421","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349982420"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349982682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349982681"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349983356","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349983356"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349984197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349984197"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" KAZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349987293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349987292"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BALI"," userResponse":" BALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349987592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349987592"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349988337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349988337"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349988627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349988626"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349988717","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349988717"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349989805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349989804"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349990055","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349990055"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349990691","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349990690"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349991749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349991749"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIO"," userResponse":" WALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349991926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349991925"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349992697","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349992696"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADENI"," userResponse":" MADENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349993188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349993188"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349996326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349996325"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349996898","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349996898"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349996961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349996961"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349997838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349997837"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349998249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349998249"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349998332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349998332"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349999330","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349999329"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548349999532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548349999532"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350000239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350000239"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350000752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350000752"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350000945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350000944"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350001729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350001728"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHATI"," userResponse":" DHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350004705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350004704"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350004801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350004801"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350005827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350005825"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350007453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350007453"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITUMIA"," userResponse":" ANAITUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350008768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350008767"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350009219","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350009219"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350009670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350009670"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350010841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350010840"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOHITAJI"," userResponse":" WANAOHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350011525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350011525"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350012114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350012114"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350014698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350014697"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350015387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350015387"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350016501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350016501"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUPENDA"," userResponse":" HUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350017187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350017186"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350018560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350018560"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHI"," userResponse":" KUFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350021315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350021315"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPENDI"," userResponse":" HAPENDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350022120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350022120"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGOMVI"," userResponse":" UGOMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350022880","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350022879"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350023391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350023390"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITA"," userResponse":" VITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350026781","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350026780"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWAALIKA"," userResponse":" HUWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350027801","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350027800"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350028889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350028887"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350029669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350029668"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350030348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350030348"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350030761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350030761"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKA"," userResponse":" DUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350031308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350031308"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350034874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350034873"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWATEMBELEA"," userResponse":" HUWATEMBELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350035910","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350035909"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAGONJWA"," userResponse":" WAGONJWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350036455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350036455"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350037193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350037193"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZEE"," userResponse":" WAZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350038072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350038072"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350038537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350038536"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350039081","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350039081"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350042120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350042120"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350043410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350043410"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" APITAPO"," userResponse":" APITAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350044367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350044366"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350045103","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350045103"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350045438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350045438"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350046043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350046043"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350047029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350047029"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350049200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350049199"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350050102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350050101"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350052888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350052888"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350053996","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350053996"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" HUFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350054197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350054196"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350054879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350054878"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350056469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350056468"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350057312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350057312"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350057495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350057495"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350058010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350058009"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350058605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350058604"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350059050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350059049"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350059528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350059527"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350060287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350060286"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350061653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350061653"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIANGALIENI"," userResponse":" ZIANGALIENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350063961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350063961"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350064135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350064133"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350064290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350064290"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350064915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350064915"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350065379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350065378"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350065912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350065911"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350066399","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350066398"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350066938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350066938"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350069666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350069665"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350069752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350069751"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350080294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350080294"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350087864","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350087863"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e3325903-61a5-4e1f-8430-d7ed8a2340aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350100958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350100958"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-8-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350106551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350106551"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-8-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350112796","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350112796"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-9-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350118143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350118143"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-6-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350124336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350124336"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350131754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350131754"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350136639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350136639"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_7-4-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350142635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350142635"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_5-8-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350148530","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350148530"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_9-4-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350153970","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350153970"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350159804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350159804"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350164721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350164721"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350170008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350170008"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_6-0-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350174853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350174853"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e0c0b79e-5461-405e-bdc9-f5ca2656914d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub3.16"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_6-0-3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350185778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350185778"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f346cc1d-2ec3-4428-8d5c-f44d09426e72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350187752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350187752"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f346cc1d-2ec3-4428-8d5c-f44d09426e72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350189351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350189351"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f346cc1d-2ec3-4428-8d5c-f44d09426e72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350191457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350191457"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f346cc1d-2ec3-4428-8d5c-f44d09426e72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350193050","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350193050"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f346cc1d-2ec3-4428-8d5c-f44d09426e72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350201841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350201841"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f346cc1d-2ec3-4428-8d5c-f44d09426e72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350202613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350202613"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f346cc1d-2ec3-4428-8d5c-f44d09426e72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350203439","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350203439"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f346cc1d-2ec3-4428-8d5c-f44d09426e72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350213089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350213089"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f346cc1d-2ec3-4428-8d5c-f44d09426e72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350213191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350213191"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f346cc1d-2ec3-4428-8d5c-f44d09426e72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350349587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350349585"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f346cc1d-2ec3-4428-8d5c-f44d09426e72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350349696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350349696"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1d6b439b-8e7f-4a04-a70e-d77bb6e5a02b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350356491","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350356491"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 1d6b439b-8e7f-4a04-a70e-d77bb6e5a02b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350365789","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350365789"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 563f482d-47ea-4231-ba8c-801d11f4ad63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350381027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350381026"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 563f482d-47ea-4231-ba8c-801d11f4ad63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350384008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350384008"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 563f482d-47ea-4231-ba8c-801d11f4ad63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350384144","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350384144"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 563f482d-47ea-4231-ba8c-801d11f4ad63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350391353","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350391353"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9daec751-d7a9-465f-8d78-656178ca2d9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350402875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350402875"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9daec751-d7a9-465f-8d78-656178ca2d9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350403388","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350403388"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9daec751-d7a9-465f-8d78-656178ca2d9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350403514","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350403514"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9daec751-d7a9-465f-8d78-656178ca2d9a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350410637","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350410637"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b48f5f24-f76d-4761-83df-4f6be86ef5b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350427310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350427310"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b48f5f24-f76d-4761-83df-4f6be86ef5b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350429934","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350429933"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b48f5f24-f76d-4761-83df-4f6be86ef5b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350430037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350430037"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b48f5f24-f76d-4761-83df-4f6be86ef5b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350440286","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350440286"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b09ffd9e-c6ca-4312-b17d-45a533a5d1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350444359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350444359"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b09ffd9e-c6ca-4312-b17d-45a533a5d1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350445946","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350445945"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b09ffd9e-c6ca-4312-b17d-45a533a5d1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350450413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350450413"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b09ffd9e-c6ca-4312-b17d-45a533a5d1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350452023","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350452023"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b09ffd9e-c6ca-4312-b17d-45a533a5d1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350456022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350456022"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b09ffd9e-c6ca-4312-b17d-45a533a5d1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350458031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350458031"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b09ffd9e-c6ca-4312-b17d-45a533a5d1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350458198","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350458198"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b09ffd9e-c6ca-4312-b17d-45a533a5d1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350465544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350465544"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b09ffd9e-c6ca-4312-b17d-45a533a5d1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350471175","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350471175"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b09ffd9e-c6ca-4312-b17d-45a533a5d1a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350513287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350513287"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350518500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350518500"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350522867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350522867"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350522868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350522868"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350524637","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350524636"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350528823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350528823"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350531600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350531600"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350535480","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350535480"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350535916","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350535915"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350536018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350536018"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350537677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350537676"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350542504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350542504"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350547109","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350547109"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350552568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350552568"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350556850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350556849"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350558183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350558183"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350562711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350562711"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350567163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350567163"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350569143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350569143"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f545b0f5-4040-43b3-a8ac-2ec48abd529d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350579342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350579341"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350579734","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350579734"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350579971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350579971"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350580294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350580294"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350580535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350580535"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350584022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350584021"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350584321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350584321"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350585235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350585234"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350585662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350585662"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350588652","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350588652"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350588945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350588945"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350589802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350589802"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350590478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350590477"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350591234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350591233"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350591564","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350591563"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350591847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350591846"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350592164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350592164"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350592438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350592438"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350596149","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350596149"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350596541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350596540"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350596787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350596786"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350597112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350597112"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350597351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350597351"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350600837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350600836"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350601137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350601137"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350602062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350602062"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350602495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350602494"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350605419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350605419"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350605721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350605720"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350606569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350606568"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350607248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350607247"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350607997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350607996"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350608337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350608337"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350608621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350608621"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350608948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350608947"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350609221","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350609221"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350612685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350612683"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350612784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350612784"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350700454","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350700454"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0644b467-eff0-4a64-b8e7-557d92c299a1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350700608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350700607"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 077ae011-82ad-45ea-a43e-2df32c765233"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350721141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350721140"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_I_O"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350727768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350727767"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_O_E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350734403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350734403"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_O_I"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350741071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350741071"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_E_O"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350747752","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350747752"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_A_I"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350754389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350754388"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_E_O"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350761030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350761030"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_E_O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350767656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350767656"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_A_U"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350775198","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350775198"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_A_U"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350785549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350785549"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_A_U"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350792184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350792183"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_O_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350798911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350798911"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_U_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350808497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350808497"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_I_U_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350816834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350816833"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_I_U_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350825247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350825247"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fa4688fc-30a2-40b8-aa1b-445fc79e1654"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_I_U_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350834567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350834567"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 21909ff5-0ff3-401d-a31a-7d96b1ed87e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350840146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350840146"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 21909ff5-0ff3-401d-a31a-7d96b1ed87e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350845585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350845584"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 21909ff5-0ff3-401d-a31a-7d96b1ed87e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_2-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350850832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350850832"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 21909ff5-0ff3-401d-a31a-7d96b1ed87e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_3-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350856762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350856762"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 21909ff5-0ff3-401d-a31a-7d96b1ed87e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350861956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350861956"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 21909ff5-0ff3-401d-a31a-7d96b1ed87e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350867732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350867731"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 21909ff5-0ff3-401d-a31a-7d96b1ed87e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350877046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350877046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 21909ff5-0ff3-401d-a31a-7d96b1ed87e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350883628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350883628"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 21909ff5-0ff3-401d-a31a-7d96b1ed87e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350888977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350888977"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 21909ff5-0ff3-401d-a31a-7d96b1ed87e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350890432","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350890431"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 21909ff5-0ff3-401d-a31a-7d96b1ed87e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_L.bub2.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350902234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350902234"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 8d4c594e-fee9-4be2-bfc7-a1d687c3cbd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350903310","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350903310"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 8d4c594e-fee9-4be2-bfc7-a1d687c3cbd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350908739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350908739"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 8d4c594e-fee9-4be2-bfc7-a1d687c3cbd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350909809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350909809"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 8d4c594e-fee9-4be2-bfc7-a1d687c3cbd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350912718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350912718"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 8d4c594e-fee9-4be2-bfc7-a1d687c3cbd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350913758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350913758"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 8d4c594e-fee9-4be2-bfc7-a1d687c3cbd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350914414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350914414"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 8d4c594e-fee9-4be2-bfc7-a1d687c3cbd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350914519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350914519"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 8d4c594e-fee9-4be2-bfc7-a1d687c3cbd3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350922371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350922371"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b2ce66e3-4199-47ef-868e-132fc63eb53e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350922594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350922594"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b2ce66e3-4199-47ef-868e-132fc63eb53e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350923556","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350923556"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b2ce66e3-4199-47ef-868e-132fc63eb53e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350924843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350924842"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b2ce66e3-4199-47ef-868e-132fc63eb53e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350925074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350925073"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b2ce66e3-4199-47ef-868e-132fc63eb53e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350925213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350925213"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" b2ce66e3-4199-47ef-868e-132fc63eb53e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350935715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350935715"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350935944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350935944"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350936933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350936931"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350938226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350938226"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350941208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350941208"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350942051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350942051"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350942363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350942363"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350943595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350943595"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350947128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350947128"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350948113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350948113"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350948369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350948369"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350949339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350949339"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350952246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350952245"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350953292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350953292"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350953773","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350953772"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350958323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350958322"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350958429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350958429"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 76a2cfa9-9d1d-4c43-98dd-d58fe42efe2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350974892","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350974892"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f3bfcaea-13ee-4b53-b87f-380cc446d3be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350981305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350981304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f3bfcaea-13ee-4b53-b87f-380cc446d3be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350982911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350982910"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f3bfcaea-13ee-4b53-b87f-380cc446d3be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350985664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350985664"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f3bfcaea-13ee-4b53-b87f-380cc446d3be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350987253","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350987253"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f3bfcaea-13ee-4b53-b87f-380cc446d3be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350989661","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350989660"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f3bfcaea-13ee-4b53-b87f-380cc446d3be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350991239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350991239"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f3bfcaea-13ee-4b53-b87f-380cc446d3be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350996644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350996644"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f3bfcaea-13ee-4b53-b87f-380cc446d3be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350998669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350998668"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f3bfcaea-13ee-4b53-b87f-380cc446d3be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548350998828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548350998828"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f3bfcaea-13ee-4b53-b87f-380cc446d3be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351011041","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351011041"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9ea2ff9c-63ed-4a24-94dd-1435c5d215df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351015590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351015590"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9ea2ff9c-63ed-4a24-94dd-1435c5d215df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351017168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351017168"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9ea2ff9c-63ed-4a24-94dd-1435c5d215df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351020674","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351020674"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9ea2ff9c-63ed-4a24-94dd-1435c5d215df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351022269","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351022268"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9ea2ff9c-63ed-4a24-94dd-1435c5d215df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351025550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351025550"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9ea2ff9c-63ed-4a24-94dd-1435c5d215df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351027123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351027123"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9ea2ff9c-63ed-4a24-94dd-1435c5d215df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351033455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351033454"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9ea2ff9c-63ed-4a24-94dd-1435c5d215df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351035499","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351035498"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9ea2ff9c-63ed-4a24-94dd-1435c5d215df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351035737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351035737"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9ea2ff9c-63ed-4a24-94dd-1435c5d215df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351048673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351048673"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351053629","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351053629"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351057688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351057688"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351061191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351061190"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351065455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351065455"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351069865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351069865"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351074838","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351074838"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351079085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351079085"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351082913","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351082913"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351084794","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351084794"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351088681","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351088681"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351091698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351091698"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_5v4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351096015","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351096014"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351101380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351101380"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351104995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351104994"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351107371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351107370"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351110200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351110199"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351112019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351112019"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351113963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351113963"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 19a06e80-27cb-4be4-a24f-10ff58bb69c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_2v9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351125032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351125032"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c93c47a8-a62c-4c31-ae38-5e7d2e9df1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" IMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351130343","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351130343"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c93c47a8-a62c-4c31-ae38-5e7d2e9df1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351131922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351131922"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c93c47a8-a62c-4c31-ae38-5e7d2e9df1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351134592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351134592"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c93c47a8-a62c-4c31-ae38-5e7d2e9df1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ILIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKI"," userResponse":" ILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351136186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351136186"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c93c47a8-a62c-4c31-ae38-5e7d2e9df1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" INGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351142204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351142204"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c93c47a8-a62c-4c31-ae38-5e7d2e9df1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" INGIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351143802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351143800"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c93c47a8-a62c-4c31-ae38-5e7d2e9df1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" IMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351150365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351150365"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c93c47a8-a62c-4c31-ae38-5e7d2e9df1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-I.rand.24__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351152413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351152412"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c93c47a8-a62c-4c31-ae38-5e7d2e9df1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351152568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351152568"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c93c47a8-a62c-4c31-ae38-5e7d2e9df1e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-I.rand.24__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" IMEJAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351207730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351207730"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351210182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351210182"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351212969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351212969"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351240609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351240609"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351242891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351242891"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351245174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351245174"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351269464","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351269464"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351289359","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351289357"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351289466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351289466"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANGAPI"," userResponse":" MANGAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351300413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351300413"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351311361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351311361"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351318007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351318006"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" c8b7c6cd-28cb-44c0-a1a3-afa6a946f320"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je una meno mangapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351329341","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351329341"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e4284fea-50f1-472d-9319-611b54bfe482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351335236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351335236"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e4284fea-50f1-472d-9319-611b54bfe482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351342332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351342332"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e4284fea-50f1-472d-9319-611b54bfe482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-9-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351348861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351348861"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e4284fea-50f1-472d-9319-611b54bfe482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-9-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351354226","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351354226"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e4284fea-50f1-472d-9319-611b54bfe482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351360275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351360275"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e4284fea-50f1-472d-9319-611b54bfe482"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351371270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351371270"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_O-A-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351374939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351374939"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_O-U-I"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351378248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351378247"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_E-U-I"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351381988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351381988"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-O-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351385305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351385305"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-E-O"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351388767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351388767"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_E-U-I"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351392864","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351392864"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-A-E"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351396173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351396173"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_I-A-E"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351399684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351399684"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-I-E"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351403104","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351403104"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-I-E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351408461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351408460"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-I-E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351418027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351418027"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9254c30b-b236-4846-bf21-0fc8d57b9119"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-I-E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351503832","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351503831"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa_kuu-chungwa-panda-panda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chungwa"," userResponse":" chungwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351521711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351521711"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa_zama-chungwa-tuli-nauli"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chungwa"," userResponse":" chungwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351540316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351540316"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_samahani-manjano-hizi-damu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351559554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351559554"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_twende-u-manjano-kali"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351577288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351577288"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijani_kijani-taratibu-uko-hebu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kijani"," userResponse":" kijani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351594723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351594723"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijani_kile-kijani-taratibu-macho"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kijani"," userResponse":" kijani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351614158","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351614157"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_manjano-kavu-samawati-ngoja"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" samawati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351631627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351631626"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_makofi-damu-kavu-samawati"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" samawati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351649548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351649548"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_yu-nili-munda-tazama"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" tazama"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351652247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351652247"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_yu-nili-munda-tazama"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" munda"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351655625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351655625"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_yu-nili-munda-tazama"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" nili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351674367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351674367"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_pumua-mpini-nili-kadhaa"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" kadhaa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351677264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351677264"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_pumua-mpini-nili-kadhaa"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" nili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351694409","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351694409"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zambarau_cheza-taja-ata-zambarau"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" zambarau"," userResponse":" zambarau"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351715186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351715186"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zambarau_cheza-taja-ata-zambarau"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351715337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351715337"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za ____________?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351725888","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351725888"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za ____________?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub3.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351731694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351731694"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za ____________?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351738896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351738896"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 42cd048f-3273-4845-8066-643216d3caa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za ____________?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351772911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351772911"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0c68af80-f98a-409d-a47c-d1885f356497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakati_kwenda-baada-wakati-katika"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wakati"," userResponse":" katika"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351775904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351775904"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0c68af80-f98a-409d-a47c-d1885f356497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakati_kwenda-baada-wakati-katika"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wakati"," userResponse":" wakati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351803262","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351803262"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0c68af80-f98a-409d-a47c-d1885f356497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wakati_katika-karibu-mimi-wakati"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" wakati"," userResponse":" wakati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351853741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351853741"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0c68af80-f98a-409d-a47c-d1885f356497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" wakati_katika-karibu-mimi-wakati"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351853848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351853848"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0c68af80-f98a-409d-a47c-d1885f356497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.rand.all.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351862307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351862307"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0c68af80-f98a-409d-a47c-d1885f356497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351870118","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351870118"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0c68af80-f98a-409d-a47c-d1885f356497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:I..I.vow.10.rand.say.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351877768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351877767"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0c68af80-f98a-409d-a47c-d1885f356497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351890490","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351890489"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0c68af80-f98a-409d-a47c-d1885f356497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa nini chumvi ni nyeupe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351890579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351890579"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" f47dc1da-a7da-41b2-b815-166cb3a4bbd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_5"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351906382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351906382"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351906767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351906767"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351907002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351907002"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351907316","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351907316"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351907550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351907549"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351910989","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351910989"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351911284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351911284"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351912187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351912187"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351912610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351912610"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351915523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351915523"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351915808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351915808"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351916650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351916650"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351917314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351917314"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351918171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351918167"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351918678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351918678"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351918961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351918960"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351919289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351919289"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351919562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351919562"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351922973","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351922973"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351923363","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351923363"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351923609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351923609"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351923943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351923943"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351924186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351924186"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351927616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351927616"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351927917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351927917"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351928827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351928826"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351929255","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351929255"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351932162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351932162"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351932451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351932450"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351933305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351933304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351933969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351933969"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351934705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351934705"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351935045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351935044"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351935327","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351935326"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351935647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351935647"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351935923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351935923"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351939451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351939451"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351939531","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351939531"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 5e9a6e9f-3c25-427f-8696-6f9ad9087696"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351974678","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351974678"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e7573fb1-e099-4ce4-a9b3-b0001c046d3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548351990102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548351990102"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e7573fb1-e099-4ce4-a9b3-b0001c046d3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352000231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352000231"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" e7573fb1-e099-4ce4-a9b3-b0001c046d3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352019209","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352019209"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352020067","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352020067"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352021092","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352021092"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352021337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352021336"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352021893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352021893"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352022458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352022458"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352022991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352022991"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352026845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352026844"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352027588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352027588"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352027983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352027983"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352028798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352028798"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352029871","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352029871"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352030665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352030665"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352033976","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352033976"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352035519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352035519"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" ANASHAMBULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352038588","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352038588"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352038853","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352038853"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352039570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352039570"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352040415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352040414"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352040870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352040870"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352041587","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352041587"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352042332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352042332"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352043547","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352043547"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFURAHI"," userResponse":" ANAFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352047052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352047051"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352048128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352048128"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOHISI"," userResponse":" ANAPOHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352048670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352048669"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352049278","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352049277"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352052047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352052046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352052168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352052168"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352063594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352063593"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 4827fab4-3bc1-4fc5-af3f-011c5a577c41"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352076237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352076236"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352077311","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352077311"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352078790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352078789"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352080185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352080185"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_9v5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352081328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352081328"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352084271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352084270"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352089108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352089108"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352094373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352094373"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352098277","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352098277"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352099184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352099183"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352102192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352102192"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352103440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352103440"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352112208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352112208"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352112220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352112211"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352112222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352112221"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 9c5ff65f-d1ef-4b33-8cc2-4a66bd08a4b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352123113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352123113"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OVAROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352126435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352126435"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OVAROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" START_OVAROLI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352130336","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352130336"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OVAROLI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352131904","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352131904"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ONA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352134108","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352134108"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ONA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352135684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352135684"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OFISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352140029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352140029"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OFISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352141580","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352141580"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352145129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352145128"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" START_OGELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352147633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352147633"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" START_OGELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352149415","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352149415"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OGELEA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352150990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352150989"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OSHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" OSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352156949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352156948"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OSHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352158526","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352158526"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" OMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352162822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352162822"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" OMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352164396","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352164396"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352166641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352166641"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.30__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352168656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352168654"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352168792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352168792"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 506f7ef8-dbe9-4501-8e8b-1dd5a3ea3337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.30__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" OA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352179259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352179259"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" NINAMPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352180780","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352180780"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352181046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352181046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352186329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352186329"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352186541","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352186541"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352187548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352187548"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREMBO"," userResponse":" MREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352187879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352187879"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352190950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352190950"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352191182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352191181"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352191894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352191893"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352193012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352193012"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352194956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352194955"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352195451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352195450"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352196178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352196178"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEMA"," userResponse":" MWEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352196791","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352196791"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352197307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352197305"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352198264","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352198264"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni mtu mwema na mwenye subira."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUBIRA"," userResponse":" SUBIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352201875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352201875"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOSUKA"," userResponse":" ALIVYOSUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352202349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352202348"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352203079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352203079"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352204666","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352204666"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINAPENDEZA"," userResponse":" ZINAPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352205225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352205225"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alivyosuka nywele zake zinapendeza sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352209332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352209332"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" AMEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352209643","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352209643"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352210376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352210376"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352210664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352210664"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352211748","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352211747"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Amezipamba na shanga za rangirangi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGIRANGI"," userResponse":" RANGIRANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352215591","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352215591"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352216364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352216364"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352216664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352216663"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352216875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352216875"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352217469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352217469"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352217724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352217724"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352218676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352218676"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352220117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352220116"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352221473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352221472"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352222129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352222128"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352223020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352223017"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shanga zake ni za rangi za kijani nyeupe nyekundu na manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352226896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352226896"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352228349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352228349"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352229289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352229289"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NISUKIE"," userResponse":" NISUKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352229680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352229680"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352230351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352230351"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352230868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352230868"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWE"," userResponse":" ZIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352231405","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352231404"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352231628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352231628"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352232401","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352232401"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352232836","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352232836"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama tafadhali nisukie nywele zangu ziwe kama za mwalimu wangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352236354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352236354"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEKUWA"," userResponse":" NINGEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352236673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352236672"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352237320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352237320"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMRI"," userResponse":" UMRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352238271","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352238271"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352240036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352240036"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEZIPAMBA"," userResponse":" NINGEZIPAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352240656","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352240655"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352241293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352241292"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352241510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352241510"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352242161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352242160"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ningekuwa na umri zaidi ningezipamba nywele zangu kwa shanga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGA"," userResponse":" SHANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352245881","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352245881"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKUA"," userResponse":" NITAKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352246453","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352246452"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352247568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352247568"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352248163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352248163"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352248912","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352248911"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352249354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352249354"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352252100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352252099"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352252195","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352252195"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352261337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352261336"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352271040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352271039"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:O..O.vow.10.rand.say.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352277551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352277551"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 82b4e719-bf11-4b99-b297-1b084f8e5848"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_8"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitakua sawa kabisa na mwalimu wangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352287695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352287695"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352288280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352288280"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352289193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352289193"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352289340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352289340"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352290044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352290044"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352290732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352290731"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352291447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352291447"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352292022","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352292022"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352292246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352292246"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352292733","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352292733"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja Hamisi na babake walienda kununua sare ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352296225","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352296225"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONEKANA"," userResponse":" ANAONEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352296743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352296743"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZURI"," userResponse":" MZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352297347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352297347"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352298152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352298151"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352299059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352299059"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaonekana mzuri sana Hamisi alifikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ALIFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352301990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352301989"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352302417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352302417"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352302534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352302533"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352302969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352302969"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352303482","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352303482"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352305448","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352305448"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352305963","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352305963"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shati hili ni safi sana Hamisi alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352312749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352312749"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352313441","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352313441"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352314567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352314567"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINUNULIE"," userResponse":" NINUNULIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352315122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352315121"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352315328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352315328"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352315953","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352315953"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352316867","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352316867"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352317644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352317643"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352318342","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352318342"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tafadhali baba ninunulie shati la kijani kibichi Hamisi alilia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILIA"," userResponse":" ALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352321270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352321269"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352322339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352322339"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINANUNUA"," userResponse":" NINANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352323123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352323122"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352323296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352323296"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352323739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352323739"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352324827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352324827"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352326044","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352326044"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352326893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352326893"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Leo ninanunua sare ya shule pekee baba alisema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352329727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352329727"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SINA"," userResponse":" SINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352330100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352330100"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352330868","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352330868"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZINGINE"," userResponse":" ZINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352331242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352331242"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352331886","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352331885"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352332431","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352332431"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352332802","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352332800"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352333300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352333300"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352334154","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352334154"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352334874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352334874"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352335391","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352335391"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sina pesa zingine za kununua shati kama hilo baba alisema tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352338749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352338749"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352339763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352339763"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352340016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352340016"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352340575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352340575"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352341850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352341849"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIZOBAKI"," userResponse":" ZILIZOBAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352342297","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352342297"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352343047","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352343046"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352343599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352343599"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352343776","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352343776"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352344374","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352344374"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352345248","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352345248"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kulikuwa na pesa zilizobaki za kununua shati la kijani kibichi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBICHI"," userResponse":" KIBICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352348561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352348561"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMISI"," userResponse":" HAMISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352349948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352349947"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352350911","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352350909"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352353731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352353728"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352353903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352353903"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352363308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352363307"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352373223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352373222"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 396b736f-2c00-4b9a-83bb-a3a867658364"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352384519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352384519"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2fec71dc-2d09-4883-b771-fb13d74af37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352390203","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352390203"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2fec71dc-2d09-4883-b771-fb13d74af37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352399420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352399419"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2fec71dc-2d09-4883-b771-fb13d74af37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352530052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352530052"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 2fec71dc-2d09-4883-b771-fb13d74af37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_M.bub3.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352530164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352530164"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fdd68cfd-c679-4c30-bfd0-45379e3b3a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352542272","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352542272"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fdd68cfd-c679-4c30-bfd0-45379e3b3a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352550207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352550207"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fdd68cfd-c679-4c30-bfd0-45379e3b3a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.22__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352562112","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352562111"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fdd68cfd-c679-4c30-bfd0-45379e3b3a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352580608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352580603"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" fdd68cfd-c679-4c30-bfd0-45379e3b3a43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548352580709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548352580709"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190124_195953"," gameId":" 0d5c9d8a-86a9-483d-8c0c-8f0e23843828"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}